Another
post popular hosting website is called
CloudFlare. So, we're going to go ahead
and click this start for free and it's
going to load and I'm going to continue
with GitHub again
and continue with my account. And this
is access this is basically once again
asking if Cloudflare can use your GitHub
to log in and you're going to authorize
that.
And now Cloudflare knows who I am. Um,
so,
um, we've brought up this nice thing.
Um, let's come here to our account home.
Um,
finish the walk through. Okay. So,
sorry. We're going to click on developer
platform and we're going to click start
building. And it's going to bring us to
this workers and pages. And then it's
going to say, how do you want to deploy?
So, here you could just directly upload
your files. Um, or you could connect
GitHub. We aren't actually. So this is
if we had built like
a a dynamic website, but what we've
built is a vanilla JavaScript website.
So what we're going to do is we're going
to go to this looking to deploy to pages
and click get started. Now it says
import an existing git repository. So
we're going to go ahead and click get
started or we could drag and drop our
files here and it would upload them. So
if you wanted you could open up your
finder, drag in the files and you'd be
good to go. But I would rather deploy
from a git repository. So I'm going to
click get started.
And it says deploy a site from your
account. Um, we want to connect to
GitHub. So, we're going to click connect
to GitHub. We're going to continue. And
this page should look shockingly
familiar at this point. GitHub is
wondering if you want Cloudflare to use
all of your repositories or only
specific ones. We're going to go with
only specific ones. And we're going to
go with our dice roller. And we're going
to hit install and authorize.
All right.
Now
um
we're here um and so we'll click connect
to GitHub continue.
All right. So now we can automatically
deploy um whenever we make a pull
request to our GitHub repository. So
basically whenever we make a change to a
branch it will redeploy just like
Verscell just like Netlefi it will
redeploy. Um, and we said we wanted it
only to have access to specific um,
repositories
and we said that we want it to have
access to dice roller. So, this is on
GitHub. Uh, let's come back over to
Cloudflare.
Oh, click login. I got logged out, I
guess.
Okay. on developer platform.
[snorts] Start building.
Get started with pages. Get started with
GitHub. And now that we've got our
account logged in, it'll show up here.
We can select the repository we want.
This is our dice roll repository. So
then we're going to click begin setup.
So a couple things you'll want to do. If
you merge your code with main, you'll
leave this production branch as main. I
didn't. I left mine on a branch called
deploy. So you're going to go ahead and
use that. If you used a framework, you
could go ahead and select it. We didn't.
So, we're going to use none. And you can
go ahead and leave everything else as it
was. Your root directory, you could
change where um it deployed from. So, if
your index.html wasn't in the main
folder, you could choose a different
folder. But ours is in the main folder.
So, we're going to go ahead and click
save and deploy. And this is going to
load for a couple of seconds. And so,
it's initializing our build environment.
And now it's going out, grabbing our
code, copying it over, it's building our
application, and then it's going to
deploy it to Cloudflare's global
network. And loads for a second longer.
Success. 11 files uploaded in 1.73
seconds. And now we can continue to our
project. Once we're here, we can see
that we've got dice roller-
nfy.pages.dev.
And we can go ahead and open it. And
here it is. And we can roll our dice
just like we did before. We can freeze
them.